(Sheldon:)That's ridiculous.
I am a grown man.
(Sheldon:)I am a professional scientist.
(Sheldon:)And I currently occupy
the moral high ground.
(Mrs Cooper:)Go to your room.
(Sheldon:)But I occupy the moral high ground.
(Sheldon:)But I'm a professional scientist.
(Mrs:)Go to your room!
(Sheldon:)I'm a grown man.
(Raj:)Can we please get back to the game?
(Leonard:)In a minute.
I don't understand why any success
(Leonard:)you have in acting is more important
than any I have in science.
(Penny:)Okay, if you do
something cool in science,
(Penny:)you might change the world.
(Penny:)If I become a famous actress...
(Penny:)I'm not gonna tell you why movie
stars are the best. They just are.
(Amy:)I'm surprised you guys never
talked about this stuff.
(Leonard:)Like you and Sheldon have
everything figured out?
(Amy:)Actually, our relationship agreement
covers a wide array of scenarios,
(Amy:)including career changes,
financial instability,